<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Tour Guide (Bari)</string>
    
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <!-- navigation menu list* -->
    <string name="nav_1">Restaurants</string>
    <string name="nav_2">Food</string>
    <string name="nav_3">Attractions</string>
    <string name="nav_4">Night Life</string>

    <!-- Restaurant Names -->
    <string name="rino">La Uascezze</string>
    <string name="gambero">Il Gambero</string>
    <string name="travi">Osteria Le Travi</string>
    <string name="arpie">Osteria Le Arpie</string>

    <!-- Food Names -->
    <string name="patate_riso_cozze">Patate Riso e Cozze</string>
    <string name="fave_cicorie">Fave e Cicoria</string>
    <string name="orecchiette_rapa">Orecchiette alle Cime di Rapa</string>
    <string name="focaccia">Focaccia di Bari</string>
    <string name="panzerotti">Panzerotti Fritti</string>

    <!-- Attractions Names -->
    <string name="san_nicola">San Nicola</string>
    <string name="ferris_wheel">Ferris wheel</string>
    <string name="petruzzelli">Teatro Petruzzelli</string>
    <string name="viasparano">Via Sparano</string>

    <!-- Night Life Names -->
    <string name="el_chiringuito">El Chiringuito</string>
    <string name="faros">Faros</string>
    <string name="barivecchia">Bari Vecchia</string>


    <!-- Description Restaurants -->
    <string name="la_uascezze">La Uascezze offers its customers a wide selection of typical products from the city of Bari in which they combine the best taste and genuineness. it is a MUST if you are in the city.</string>
    <string name="il_gambero">A place where you can taste good fish dishes, but certainly good food, spaghetti with seafood, grilled vegetables, mixed fried, and much more.</string>
    <string name="le_travi">If the love for food brings you to bari and you want to taste a bit of this old town’s wonders, make sure you visit this place. It runs in a very old building, that kept it’s charm and architecture.</string>
    <string name="le_arpie">Authentic and historical tavern in the heart of Bari Vecchia, accessed by an arch, inside a narrow courtyard..table outdoors in good weather, friendly and simple service, excellent cuisine of Bari, Without great pretensions, you spend a nice evening without spending crazy figures.</string>

    <!-- Description Food -->
    <string name="patate_cozze_description">A dish of both land and sea, the "tiella" barese inebriates the streets around the Basilica of San Nicola for over four centuries. every Bari family prepares it differently: who puts more potatoes, more rice, sometimes whole tomatoes, some add salsa and who, again, neither of the above and who, on the other hand, also add courgette.</string>
    <string name="fave_cicoria_description">Fave e cicoria (fava beans and chicory) is a popular dish in Puglia, the heel of Italy’s boot. It takes inspiration from Egyptian bean purées across the Mediterranean, and uses a few quality ingredients in similar ways. Bitter greens balance the warm, hearty ﬂavor of the bean puree perfectly in this simple 4-ingredient dish.</string>
    <string name="orecchiette_cime_rapa_description">Puglia’s sun-soaked landscape in southern Italy is celebrated for its signature dish, orecchiette with broccoli rabe. The pasta’s “little ears,” as “orecchiette” translates, are a homemade pasta made exclusively in southern italy.</string>
    <string name="focaccia_description">Focaccia Barese is a street food with very light dough, different than pizza. It’s topped with Olio Terra di Bari, oven baked black olives and tomatoes. A speciality you must try without  . </string>
    <string name="panzerotti_description">Strictly fried and strictly accompanied by a cold beer: praise to the panzerotto. A must, a symbol, a tradition. Bari without him would not be the same and the people without the long-awaited "panzerottata" would have one less reason to look forward to Christmas Eve.</string>

    <!-- Description Attractions -->
    <string name="san_nicola_descriprion">When sailors from Bari saved the relics of Saint Nicholas from his resting place in Muslim controlled Myra in 1087, they began a tradition which, in 2012, celebrates its 925th anniversary: the Festa di San Nicola. An amazing experience to enjoy, with thousands of people in the city of bari celebrating on the streets.</string>
    <string name="ferris_wheel_description">Ferris wheel was inaugurated on December 6 2017 and is perhaps the most photographed and recounted attraction of Bari in recent months having a direct view on the mediterranean sea.</string>
    <string name="petruzzelli_description">The Teatro Petruzzelli is the largest theatre of the city of Bari and the fourth Italian theatre by size. A magnificent theatre with a rich and tragic history back to its splendor.</string>
    <string name="viasparano_description">Via Sparano is the main walking/Shopping street that goes from the main station to the sea front. Full os shops of all kinds it is defenitely a must see.</string>

    <!-- Description Night Life -->
    <string name="chiringuito_description">What better way to enjoy yourself than to enjoy a nice fresh beer on the sea. Located near the bar El Chiringuito, the old port as well as offering a wonderful show of variety of fish in the morning during the market, in the evening offers those who want a mystical and engaging location where to go together to enjoy the lights that are reflected on maybe water with a nice frozen Peroni.</string>
    <string name="faros_description">When you want a special aperitif, FAROS is the ideal place. Special the qualities of beers with an almost infinite variety. The service is excellent and the manager treats everyone like old friends. The atmosphere is serene with good music. I recommend this place even for an evening at 2.</string>
    <string name="barivecchia_description">Bari Vecchia is a great centre for nightlife, full of bars, restaurants and street food variety, all this in the most historical location of bari, the old city.</string>
</resources>
